MATTHEW SEAO

UX Designer

Contact



(614) 329-5509



mattseao@outlook.com



Columbus, OH



linkedin.com/in/mattseao

Education

03/2023

Certificate in UX Design

CareerFoundry

Key Skills

- User Research
- Competitive Analysis
- User Personas
- Journey Maps
- User Flows
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Frontend Development

Tools

- Figma
- Adobe Photoshop
- Visual Studio Code

Awards

03/2013

Hip Hop Expo 1v1 Champion Dance

Profile

UX Designer with a background in customer service roles. Experienced with communication and creating visual designs. Skilled with developing solutions that suit the needs of customers and users.

UX/UI Projects

03/2022 - 02/2023

Columbus, OH

Expert App for CareerFoundry

- Designed a social media platform that connected professionals to everyday persons in various mediums of communication.
- Defined user needs and goals through the means of user research, competitive analysis, and interviews to create user personas, journey flows, and site maps.
- Created wireframes, mockups, multiple prototypes, and a style guide that went through several rounds of usability tests to ensure a user-centric experience.

Work Experience

07/2022 - 11/2022

Columbus, OH

Small Parcel Delivery at Best Buy

- Organized and sorted products
- Created and executed routes for assignments.
- Delivered small to medium packages from store locations directly to customers homes.

10/2021 - 12/2021

Groveport, OH

Live Chat Specialist at Gap Inc Direct

- Helped customers troubleshoot order and/or website issues.
- Assisted through means of live online chat and live calls.
- De-escalated hostile situations if necessary.